pwnieexpress.com 2018-09-10

# Privacy Policy

Request Removal of Your Data **

Scope – Privacy Policy, Terms of Service and Third Party Links      

Privacy Policy. 

**This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to information we collect, receive, or use on or in connection with websites owned or controlled by Rapid Focus Security, Inc. or its affiliated companies (“Rapid Focus” or “Pwnie Express” or “we” or “us”), including www.pwnieexpress.com, applications, products, features, services, marketing, email or other site-related electronic communications, whether online or offline, or any portion thereof (collectively, the “Service”). Affiliated companies are entities that control, are controller by or are under common control with Rapid Focus Security, Inc.

 **Terms of Service.** This Privacy Policy and the Pwnie Express Terms of Service (“Terms of Service”), which can be found at https://www.pwnieexpress.com/terms-of-service, and is incorporated herein by reference, are an agreement (collectively, this “Agreement”) between Pwnie Express and you (“You” or “your” or “you), a user of the Service. By accessing or using the Service, you acknowledge and agree to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. If you choose to not agree with the Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service, you may not use the Service.

**Third Party Websites or Services.** The Services contains links to third party websites or services, including third party applications or software that you may choose to integrate with the Service through Pwnie Express’ website (“Third Party Services”). Please be aware that this policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, the content or privacy practices of such Third Party Services. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave Pwnie Express’ Service and to read the privacy statements of any other site, application or software that you use, which may collect information about you. 

**Information Collection.**  We may collect and receive information that identifies you ("Personal Information") and other information and data related to you and your use of the Service (“Other Information” and together with Personal Information, “Information”):  
 **  
Personal Information About You.**

  * Information that you provide to us when you register for an account, such as your name, address, profile image, title, phone number, and email address; 
  * Information that you provide to us when you purchase a product or service, including, without limitation, payment, billing, contact, physical address, and related information; 
  * Information that you provide if you email, phone, contact or communicate with us or our third party service providers, such as your name, title, email address or phone number.

**Other Information You Provide.**

  * Information that you provide to us if you participate in a promotion;
  * Information that you provide or upload while using the Service, including company information related to a security review request or for use in a security profile or for internal assessment purposes. You may also upload Personal Information about your company or vendor contacts (such as their names, titles, and other contact information);
  * Information from public databases and third parties;

**Usage Information.**

  * Traffic and usage information generated from your visit to the Service, for example: traffic data, pages you visit, features you use, browser information, operating system, IP address, cookie information, and the type of device that you use to access the Service;
  * De-identified, aggregate information about you and our other users, such as the numbers and frequency of users and their characteristics and information about similar groups of users, or users that live in a particular geographical area. This data is used in the aggregate as a statistical measure and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This aggregate information generally is collected through the use of cookies or beacons;
  * De-identified, aggregate data related to the security reviews conducted using Pwnie Express;
  * Information regarding the videos you view on the Service. **  
**

**Children Under the Age of 13.  **

  * The Service and its content are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or allow people under the age of 13 to register for the Service or provide any Information to or on our websites. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [marketing@pwnieexpress.com](mailto:marketing@pwnieexpress.com).

**Tracking Technologies We Use.    
**We may use one or more of the following tracking technologies, and similar future tracking technologies, to automatically collect Information: cookies, local shared objects, web beacons, unique telephone numbers, general log information and referral information from third-party services.

  * "Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in the Service are visited and by how many people. We give users a choice whether to opt in to the use of cookies during their first visit to our site. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. The "Help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use many features of the Service.
  * “Log Data” Our server logs collect routine information about how people access our Site including for example: IP address, the date and time you visited this Site, the address of any website you linked through to get to this Site.
  * "Web beacons," also known as an Internet tags, pixel tags or clear GIFs, link web pages to web servers and their cookies. Web beacons can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails, to collect certain types of information from your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the content, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the content was viewed.
  * "Local shared objects," sometimes known as Flash cookies, may be used to store your preferences or display content based upon what you have viewed on various websites to personalize your visit. **  
**

**How we use information.** We may use the information that we collect or receive about you for any of the following purposes: 

  * To provide, operate, maintain, troubleshoot, improve, and promote the Service;
  * To enable you to access and use the Service, including uploading, downloading, collaborating and sharing content and information with other users or third parties;
  * To contact you for account management, customer service, billing and support reasons, and to process and complete transactions, including sending billing, invoice, and related account information;
  * To send transactional messages, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests;
  * To send you technical notices, product or service updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * To send promotional communications, such as providing you with information about products, services, features, newsletters, offers, promotions, events and updates;
  * To monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Service and for marketing, advertising, administrative, account management, analytical, research, optimization, and other purposes. For example, we may use statistical analyses of usage data in order to measure interest in the various areas of the Service, for research and development purposes, or to inform business prospects or partners about the use of the Service and our website;
  * To investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to the Service, and other illegal activities;

To personalize the Service’s content, features or advertisements; **

THIRD PARTY SERVICES      

**  
We may transfer data about you, including Personal Data, as follows: **

Service Providers.  

**We may contract with third-party service providers to perform functions for us. These service providers may be given Personal Information or access to it for the purpose of doing so. Service Providers will be contractually bound to maintain the security and confidentiality of such information and use it only under our direction.  **

Business Transfers.  

**We reserve the right to transfer some or all of the information we have about you as part of a business transfer of some or all of our assets to another company.  **

Disclosures for Legal Reasons.  

**We reserve the right to disclose information about you when we are required to do so by law or regulation, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena or any other valid legal process. We may also disclose the information in response to a law enforcement agency request or when we believe such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to safeguard anyone’s property or safety.  **

INFORMATION SHARING      

Retention. 

**We may retain your Information as long as you are a registered user, or to meet our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements. When we no longer have a business need to process your Information, we may either delete it or aggregate it for anonymous use. You may also request that we delete your Personal Information at any time. If we cannot delete or aggregate some of your Information, such as when it is archived in our backup systems, then we will store, but not otherwise further process, that Information until it is deleted pursuant to our data retention policies.  
 **  
Service Providers.**  We may engage service providers to assist us in delivering the Services and to support our business. We may share your Information, including, without limitation, Personal Information, with such service providers subject to obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures, and on the condition that the third parties use your Information only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions. Additional information regarding the service providers that may process your Information on our behalf (“subprocessors”) will be provided upon request.  
 **  
Payment Processors.  **If you utilize any paid Service, we will share your payment information with our bank to process payments.  
 **  
Authorized Personnel.  **Our employees, agents, consultants, and contractors may have access to user Information on a need-to-know basis only. Such authorized personnel are bound by strict confidentiality obligations and our other security measures and policies.  
 **  
Business Transactions.**  If the Service or Company considers or engages in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization or sale of assets or stock, financing, or similar transaction, user Information may be shared or transferred, subject to confidentiality protections and security measures no less protective than as outlined in this Privacy Policy.  
 **  
Government, Law Enforcement or Third Parties.  **We may disclose any Information, including, without limitation, Personal Information, that we deem necessary, in our sole discretion and without your prior permission, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We also may exchange Information, including, without limitation, Personal Information, with other companies and organizations to protect the rights, property, or safety of Rapid Focus Security, Inc. and its affiliates, personnel, users, third parties, or others. We reserve the right to disclose a user’s Information, including, without limitation, Personal Information, to law enforcement and regulatory agencies if we believe, in good faith, that the user is in violation of the Terms of Service, even without a subpoena, warrant or other court order. **

RIGHT TO CHOOSE AND TO OPT-OUT      

**We provide you with the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding out collection, use and sharing of your information. **

In accordance with local law:

**

  * You can choose not to provide information to us, although your use of our site and Services will be limited.
  * You may correct, update and delete your account information, as described below.
  * You may change your choices for email subscriptions and newsletters through your user account settings, by contacting us as described below, or by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the email.
  * You will be given the choice on your first visit to our website whether to opt in to the use of cookies. You can also set your browser to refuse all or some cookies or alert you to when cookies are being sent. However, it’s important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. **  
**

If you are from certain territories (such as the European Economic Area), you may have the right to exercise additional rights available to you under applicable laws, including, in certain circumstances:

  * **Right to erasure.** You may have the right to require us to erase your Personal Information (the “right to be forgotten”).
  * **Right to object.** You may have the right to object to the processing of your Personal Information, including for direct marketing purposes.
  * **Right to restriction of processing.  **You may have the right to restrict the processing (other than storage) of your Personal Information, such as to verify the accuracy of your Personal Information or if the information is being unlawfully processed.
  * **Right to data portability.**  You may have the right to be provided with your Personal Information in a commonly used format or to require that we transmit your Personal Information directly to others.

In each case, however, we may have a right to retain certain Personal Information for legal and administrative purposes. If you would like to exercise your rights, please email us at support@pwnieexpress.com. We may require that verify your identity before we process your request.

  * **Accessing and Correcting Your Information.**  If you have a Pwnie Express account, you can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account or by emailing us at support@pwnieexpress.com. For other Personal Information we hold, we will provide you with access for any purpose including requesting that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if we are not required or permitted to retain it by law. You can contact as provided below to request such information. We cannot delete your Personal Information except by deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change or delete your Personal Information if we believe that the change would violate any law or legal requirement, if the information is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, or to protect others’ rights. We may also not remove Personal Information from our backup systems. If you have made comments via the Services and shared those comments in collaboration with others, then copies of your comments may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other website users.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION      

Security Measures. 

**We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures designed to help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the Information we collect and receive. These safeguards vary based on the sensitivity of the Information. **

Your Responsibilities.  

**The safety and security of your Information also depends on you. Where we have given you a password for access to certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Where you have chosen a password, you are responsible for ensuring that it is regularly changed and sufficiently strong. We also encourage you to use additional security measures that may be available to you via the Services, including Single Sign On (SSO) and two-factor authentication. **

No Security Guarantees.

**  Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of Information, we cannot assure you that Information will never be disclosed, altered or destroyed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.  
 **  
Changes to the Privacy Policy.  **We may change our Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, in our sole discretion. All updates and amendments are effective immediately upon notice, which we may give by any means, including, but not limited to, by posting a revised version of this Privacy Policy or other notice on our website. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to the Privacy Policy. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is reflected by the version date located at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Service after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. **

CONTACT INFORMATION.

Contact Information. 

**If you have any questions, feedback or to report a violation regarding the Privacy Policy, you may email us at support@pwnieexpress.com or contact us by mail addressed to:

Pwnie Express  
268 Summer Street, 2nd Floor  
Boston, MA. 02210  
 **  
Marketing.  **If you would like us to stop sending you marketing emails you may use the opt-out link at the bottom of any marketing email we send. Although we encourage you to use the opt-out link because it is automated, you may also send us a request at [marketing@pwnieexpress.com](mailto:marketing@pwnieexpress.com). You can also use that address to request a copy of any Personal Information you have submitted to us through this Site or that we have in our marketing files to correct the information or to delete that information from marketing use. We will endeavor to satisfy such requests within a reasonable time. We reserve the right to retain a copy in our inactive records for any legally required purposes. **

Terms and Conditions  
1\. Terms  
By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.

2\. Use License  
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Pwnie Express’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: modify or copy the materials; use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial); attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Pwnie Express’s web site; remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.  
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Pwnie Express at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

3\. Disclaimer  
The materials on Pwnie Express’s web site are provided “as is”. Pwnie Express makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Pwnie Express does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

4\. Limitations  
In no event shall Pwnie Express or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Pwnie Express’s Internet site, even if Pwnie Express or a Pwnie Express authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

5\. Revisions and Errata  
The materials appearing on Pwnie Express’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Pwnie Express does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Pwnie Express may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Pwnie Express does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.

6\. Links  
Pwnie Express has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Pwnie Express of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.

7\. Site Terms of Use Modifications  
Pwnie Express may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.

8\. Governing Law  
Any claim relating to Pwnie Express’s web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Vermont without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

**
